question_data = [
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "A person can get sunburned on a cloudy day.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "The common software-programming acronym 'I18N' comes "
                                                   "from the term 'Interlocalization'.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The first computer bug was formed by faulty wires.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia is the irrational fear of "
                                                  "long words.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Leonardo DiCaprio won an Oscar for Best Actor in 2004  s  The Aviator .",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "There aren  t any live-action clones in  Star Wars: Episode III - Revenge of the Sith .",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The programming language  Python is based off a modified version of  JavaScript .",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The proof for the Chinese Remainder Theorem used in Number Theory was NOT developed by its first "
                 "publisher, Sun Tzu.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The word  Inception  came from the 2010 blockbuster hit  Inception .",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Type 1 diabetes is a result of the liver working improperly.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                                      "question": "The first  Metal Gear  game was released for the PlayStation 1.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Big the Cat is a playable character in  Sonic Generations .", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "A bear does NOT defecate during hibernation. ",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The average woman is 5 inches 13 centimeters shorter than the average man.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "According to Norse mythology, Loki is a mother.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "The color orange is named after the fruit.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Board Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The card game  Munchkin  won the 2001 Origins Award for Best Traditional Card Game.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Scientists accidentally killed the once known world  s oldest living creature, a mollusc, "
                 "known to be aged as 507 years old.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In 2010, Twitter and the United States Library of Congress partnered together to archive every "
                 "tweet by American citizens.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Russia passed a law in 2013 which outlaws telling children that homosexuals exist.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Ewan McGregor did not know the name of the second prequel film of Star Wars during and after filming.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "In Undertale, having a  Fun Value  set to 56-57 will play the  Wrong Number Song Call .",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Board Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "There is a Donald Trump Board Game, which was made in 1989.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": " HTML  stands for Hypertext Markup Language.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Adolf Hitler was born in Australia. ", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the game  Subnautica , a  Spadefish  will attack you.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "EDM label Monstercat signs tracks instead of artists.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "The NVidia GTX 1080 gets its name because it can only render at a "
                                                   "1920x1080 screen resolution.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "According to Greek Mythology, Atlas was an Olympian God.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In Riot Games  League of Legends  the name of Halloween event is called  The Reckoning .",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The chemical element Lithium is named after the country of Lithuania.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "Donald Trump won the popular vote in the 2016 United States "
                                                  "presidential election.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The Klingon home planet is Qo  noS.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Klingons respect their disabled comrades, and those who are old, injured, and helpless.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In  Call Of Duty: World At War , the first appearance of the  PPSH-41  in  Zombies  was in the map  "
                 "Der Riese .",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The sum of any two odd integers is odd.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "New Haven is the capital city of the state of Connecticut in the United States.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "You can square root a negative number with an imaginary number  i .",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "An episode of  The Simpsons  is dedicated to Moe Szyslak  s bar rag.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Musical artist, Future, collaborated with Kendrick Lamar for the song:  Mask Off .",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The 2011 movie  The Adventures of Tintin  was directed by Steven Spielberg.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Sports", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "During Wimbledon, spectators in the grounds can buy the tennis balls that have been used in matches.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The character Plum from  No Game No Life  is a girl.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Vehicles", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                                      "question": "The term  GTO  was originated by Ferrari?",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In  Avatar: The Last Airbender  and  The Legend of Korra , Lavabending is a specialized bending "
                 "technique of Firebending.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Shang Tsung is a playable character in Mortal Kombat XL.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "The game  Jetpack Joyride  was created by  Redbrick Studios .",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Lead Singer Rivers Cuomo of American rock band Weezer attended Harvard.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Resident Evil 4, the Chicago Typewriter has infinite ammo.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                                       "question": "NCIS stands for  Navy Corps Investigative Service ",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
